[
    {
        "question": "What is the published date of CVE-2016-9733",
        "expected_answer": "2017-07-05T17:29Z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of CVE-2016-9733",
        "expected_answer": "IBM Team Concert (RTC) 4.0, 5.0 and 6.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 119762."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the exploitability score of CVE-2016-9733",
        "expected_answer": 2.3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the impact score of CVE-2016-9733",
        "expected_answer": 2.7
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the base score of CVE-2016-9733",
        "expected_answer": 5.4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the published date of CVE-2022-33248",
        "expected_answer": "2023-02-12T04:15Z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of CVE-2022-33248",
        "expected_answer": "Memory corruption in User Identity Module due to integer overflow to buffer overflow when a segement is received via qmi http."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the exploitability score of CVE-2022-33248",
        "expected_answer": 1.8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the impact score of CVE-2022-33248",
        "expected_answer": 5.9
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the base score of CVE-2022-33248",
        "expected_answer": 7.8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the published date of CVE-2022-27412",
        "expected_answer": "2022-05-09T18:15Z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of CVE-2022-27412",
        "expected_answer": "Explore CMS v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via a /page.php?id= request."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the exploitability score of CVE-2022-27412",
        "expected_answer": 3.9
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the impact score of CVE-2022-27412",
        "expected_answer": 5.9
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the base score of CVE-2022-27412",
        "expected_answer": 9.8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the published date of CVE-2023-40476",
        "expected_answer": "2024-05-03T03:15Z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of CVE-2023-40476",
        "expected_answer": "GStreamer H265 Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GStreamer. Interaction with this library is required to exploit this vulnerability but attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.\n\nThe specific flaw exists within the parsing of H265 encoded video files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21768."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the exploitability score of CVE-2023-40476",
        "expected_answer": "No data available"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the impact score of CVE-2023-40476",
        "expected_answer": "No data available"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the base score of CVE-2023-40476",
        "expected_answer": "No data available"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the published date of CVE-2022-1890",
        "expected_answer": "2023-01-26T21:15Z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of CVE-2022-1890",
        "expected_answer": "A buffer overflow in the ReadyBootDxe driver in some Lenovo Notebook products may allow an attacker with local privileges to execute arbitrary code."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the exploitability score of CVE-2022-1890",
        "expected_answer": 1.8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the impact score of CVE-2022-1890",
        "expected_answer": 5.9
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the base score of CVE-2022-1890",
        "expected_answer": 7.8
    }
]